Guide to the Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor 1967-1996 (Bulk 1974-1996) MSS.216
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
  - Harlequin Romance 1771. Danbury, Iris: The Silver Stallion. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1772. Dingwell, Joyce: Sister Pussycat. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 217)
  - Harlequin Romance 1773. Chace, Isobel: A Man of Kent. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1774. Kidd, Flora: The Legend of the Swans. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - Harlequin Romance 1775. Wibberley, Mary: Master of Saramanca. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1776. Rome, Margaret: The Island of Pearls. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - Harlequin Romance 1777. Neels, Betty: Enchanting Samantha. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1778. Peake, Lilian: A Sense of Belonging. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 220)
  - Harlequin Romance 1779. Thorpe, Kay: The Man at Kambala. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1780. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Tower of the Winds. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 221)
  - Harlequin Romance 1781. Malcolm, Margaret: Cherish this Wayward Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1782. Gillen, Lucy: Painted Wings. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 222)
  - Harlequin Romance 1783. Leigh, Roberta: Cinderella in Mink. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1784. Cork, Dorothy: The Red Plains of Jounima. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Harlequin Romance 1785. Way, Margaret: The Love Theme. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1786. Wilde, Hilary: Sweeter Than Honey. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 224)
  - Harlequin Romance 1787. Farnes, Eleanor: The Runaway Visitors. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1788. Ashton, Elizabeth: Errant Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 225)
  - Harlequin Romance 1789. Arbor, Jane: The Velvet Spur. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1790. Wibberley, Mary: Laird of Gaela. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Harlequin Romance 1791. Grierson, Linden: The Trees of Tarrentall. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1792. Burchell, Mary: Pay Me Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Harlequin Romance 1793. Britt, Katrina: The King of Spades. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1794. May, Wynne: Pink Sands. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Harlequin Romance 1795. Chace, Isobel: The Edge of Beyond. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1796. Kidd, Flora: Gallant's Fancy. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 229)
  - Harlequin Romance 1797. Dell, Belinda: The Darling Pirate. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1798. Kent, Pamela: Nile Dusk. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Harlequin Romance 1799. Stratton, Rebecca: The Bride of Romano. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1800. Leigh, Roberta: Shade of the Palms. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Harlequin Romance 1801. Neels, Betty: Uncertain Summer. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1802. Wibberley, Mary: The Benedict Man. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 232)
  - Harlequin Romance 1803. Lamb, Charlotte: A Family Affair. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1804. Danbury, Iris: The Fires of Torretta. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Harlequin Romance 1805. Malcolm, Margaret: Return to Blytheburn. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1806. Gillen, Lucy: The Pengelly Jade. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Harlequin Romance 1807. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Tree of Idleness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1808. Dingwell, Joyce: There Were Three Princes. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Harlequin Romance 1809. Bevan, Gloria: Connelly's Castle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1810. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Rocks of Arachenza. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Harlequin Romance 1811. Burchell, Mary: Strangers May Marry. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1812. Cork, Dorothy: A Promise to Keep. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Harlequin Romance 1813. Mann, Margaret: Destiny Decrees. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1814. Clemence, Ruth: A Time to Love. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Harlequin Romance 1815. Way, Margaret: Wind River. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1816. Stratton, Rebecca: Castles in Spain. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - Harlequin Romance 1817. Neels, Betty: The Gemel Ring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1818. Ford, Norrey: One Hot Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 240)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233356
  - Harlequin Romance 1819. Lewty, Marjorie: All Made of Wishes. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1820. Grierson, Linden: Rising River. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 241)
  - Harlequin Romance 1821. Pressley, Hilda: When Winter was Gone. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1822. Gillen, Lucy: The Runaway Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 242)
  - Harlequin Romance 1823. Lane, Roumelia: Across the Lagoon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1824. Wilde, Hilary: A Handful of Dreams. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 243)
  - Harlequin Romance 1825. Hoy, Elizabeth: Shadows on the Sand. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1826. Dingwell, Joyce: The Habit of Love. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 244)
  - Harlequin Romance 1827. Wibberley, Mary: Logan's Island. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1828. Malcolm, Margaret: A Bright Particular Star. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Harlequin Romance 1829. Chace, Isobel: The Dragon's Cave. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1830. Lavender, Gwyn: Falcon on the Mountain. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Harlequin Romance 1831. Peake, Lilian: Master of the House. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1832. Arbor, Jane: Meet the Sun Halfway. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Harlequin Romance 1833. Kidd, Flora: The Paper Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1834. Burchell, Mary: Song Cycle. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 248)
  - Harlequin Romance 1835. Ashton, Elizabeth: Dark Angel. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1836. Wibberley, Mary: Kyle's Kingdom. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Harlequin Romance 1837. Danbury, Iris: The Amethyst Meadows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1838. Andersen, Jan: Master of Koros. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Harlequin Romance 1839. Stratton, Rebecca: Run from the Wind. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1840. Way, Margaret: Return to Belle Amber. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Harlequin Romance 1841. Neels, Betty: The Magic of Living. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1842. Ford, Norrey: Call to the Castle. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Harlequin Romance 1843. Westwood, Gwen: Sweet Roots and Honey. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1844. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Beads of Nemesis. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 253)
  - Harlequin Romance 1845. MacLeod, Jean S.: Time Suspended. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1846. Dell, Belinda: Lake of Silver. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 254)
  - Harlequin Romance 1847. Gillen, Lucy: The Changing Years. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1848. Weale, Anne: Lord of the Sierras. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 255)
  - Harlequin Romance 1849. Chace, Isobel: The Hospital of Fatima. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1850. Peters, Sue: The Storm Within. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 256)
  - Harlequin Romance 1851. Reid, Henrietta: Dragon Island. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1852. Gray, Janice: Star Light, Star Bright. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Harlequin Romance 1853. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Road to the Border. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1854. Summers, Essie: Through All the Years. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Harlequin Romance 1855. Peake, Lilian: The Impossible Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1856. Dingwell, Joyce: The Cattleman. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Harlequin Romance 1857. Neels, Betty: Cruise to a Wedding. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1858. Stratton, Rebecca: Island of Darkness. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Harlequin Romance 1860. Bevan, Gloria: High-Country Wife. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1861. Gillen, Lucy: The Stairway to Enchantment. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 261)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233364
  - Harlequin Romance 1862. Lake, Rozella: Chateau in Provence. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1863. Way, Margaret: McCabe's Kingdom. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 262)
  - Harlequin Romance 1864. Malcolm, Margaret: Dear Tyrant (original title: Beloved Tyrant). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1865. Kidd, Flora: Stranger in the Glen. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 263)
  - Harlequin Romance 1866. Britt, Katrina: The Greater Happiness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1867. Dingwell, Joyce: Flamingo Flying South. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 264)
  - Harlequin Romance 1868. Peake, Lilian: The Dream on the Hill. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1869. Ashton, Elizabeth: The House of the Eagles. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Harlequin Romance 1870. Field, Sandra: To Trust My Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1871. Burchell, Mary: The Brave in Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Harlequin Romance 1872. Andersen, Jan: Cinnamon Hill. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1873. Danbury, Iris: A Pavement of Pearl. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Harlequin Romance 1874. Peters, Sue: Design for Destiny. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1875. May, Wynne: A Plume of Dust. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Harlequin Romance 1876. Cork, Dorothy: Gate of the Golden Gazelle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1877. Gillen, Lucy: Means to an End. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 269)
  - Harlequin Romance 1878. Dawson, Elizabeth: Isle of Dreams. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1879. Wibberley, Mary: Dark Viking. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 270)
  - Harlequin Romance 1880. Way, Margaret: Sweet Sundown. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1881. Neels, Betty: The End of the Rainbow. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Harlequin Romance 1882. Donnelly, Jane: Ride Out the Storm. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1883. Stratton, Rebecca: Autumn Concerto. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Harlequin Romance 1884. Summers, Essie: The Gold of Noon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1885. Hoy, Elizabeth: Proud Citadel. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Harlequin Romance 1886. Gray, Janice: Take All My Loves. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1887. Dingwell, Joyce: Love and Lucy Brown. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Harlequin Romance 1887. Dingwell, Joyce: Love and Lucy Brown (duplicate copy). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1888. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Bonds of Matrimony. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Harlequin Romance 1889. Way, Margaret: Reeds of Honey. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1890. Burchell, Mary: Tell Me My Fortune. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 276)
  - Harlequin Romance 1891. Ashton, Elizabeth: Scorched Wings. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1892. Britt, Katrina: The House Called Sakura. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Harlequin Romance 1893. Lake, Rozella: If Dreams Came True. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1894. Cork, Dorohy: Quicksilver Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 278)
  - Harlequin Romance 1895. Gillen, Lucy: Glen of Signs. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1896. Arbor, Jane: The Wide Fields of Home. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 279)
  - Harlequin Romance 1897. Douglas, Sheila: Westhampton Royal. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1898. Stratton, Rebecca: Firebird. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Harlequin Romance 1899. Pargeter, Margaret: Winds from the Sea. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1900. Peake, Lilian: Moonrise over the Mountains. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 281)
  - Harlequin Romance 1901. Hoy, Elizabeth: The Blue Jacaranda. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1902. Reid, Henrietta: The Man at the Helm. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 282)
  - Harlequin Romance 1903. Wibberley, Mary: Country of the Vine. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1904. Chace, Isobel: The Cornish Hearth. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 283)
  - Harlequin Romance 1905. Neels, Betty: Tabitha in Moonlight. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1906. Britt, Katrina: Take Back Your Love. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 284)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233372
  - Harlequin Romance 1907. Kidd, Flora: Enchantment in Blue. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1908. Gillen, Lucy: A Touch of Honey. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 285)
  - Harlequin Romance 1909. Thorpe, Kay: The Shifting Sands. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1910. Dingwell, Joyce: Cane Music. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 286)
  - Harlequin Romance 1911. Gray, Janice: Stormy Harvest, (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1913. Stratton, Rebecca: The Flight of the Hawk. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 287)
  - Harlequin Romance 1914. Lewty, Marjorie: Flowers in Stony Places. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1915. Whittal, Yvonne: East to Barryvale. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 288)
  - Harlequin Romance 1916. Peters, Sue: Wheels of Conflict. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1917. Summers, Essie: Anna of Strathallan. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 289)
  - Harlequin Romance 1918. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Player King. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1919. Burchell, Mary: Just a Nice Girl. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 290)
  - Harlequin Romance 1920. Lane, Roumelia: Harbour of Deceit. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1921. Neels, Betty: Heaven is Gentle. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 291)
  - Harlequin Romance 1922. Smith, Doris E.: Cotswold Honey. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1923. Bevan, Gloria: Always a Rainbow. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 292)
  - Harlequin Romance 1924. Wibberley, Mary: The Dark Isle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1925. Weston, Sophie: Beware the Huntsmen. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 293)
  - Harlequin Romance 1926. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Voice in the Thunder. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1927. Cork, Dorothy: Wandalilli Princess. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 294)
  - Harlequin Romance 1928. Gillen, Lucy: Gentle Tyrant. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1929. Donnelly, Jane: Collision Course. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 295)
  - Harlequin Romance 1930. Gillen, Lucy: Web of Silver. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1931. Gray, Janice: Lullaby of Leaves. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 296)
  - Harlequin Romance 1932. Dingwell, Joyce: The Kissing Gate. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1933. Ashton, Elizabeth: Miss Nobody From Nowhere. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 297)
  - Harlequin Romance 1934. Malcolm, Margaret: A Stranger is My Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1935. Wibberley, Mary: That Man Bryce. (Harlequin Books), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 298)
  - Harlequin Romance 1936. Burchell, Mary: Remembered Serenade. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1937. Neels, Betty: Henrietta's Own Castle. (Harlequin Books), 1975;1976 (Box 13, Folder 299)
  - Harlequin Romance 1938. Lamb, Charlotte: Sweet Sanctuary. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1939. Rome, Margaret: The Girl at Danes' Dyke. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 300)
  - Harlequin Romance 1940. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Sycamore Song. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1941. Beaty, Betty: Love and the Kentish Maid. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 301)
  - Harlequin Romance 1942. Stratton, Rebecca: The Fire and the Fury. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1943. Craven, Sara: The Garden of Dreams. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 302)
  - Harlequin Romance 1944. Peake, Lilian: Heart in the Sunlight. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1945. Chace, Isobel: The Desert Castle. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 303)
  - Harlequin Romance 1945. Chace, Isobel: The Desert Castle (other edition). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1946. Ashton, Elizabeth: Crown of Willow. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 304)
  - Harlequin Romance 1947. Burchell, Mary: The Girl in the Blue Dress. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1948. Westwood, Gwen: Ross of Silver Ridge. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 305)
  - Harlequin Romance 1949. Elver, Rose: Shining Wanderer. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1950. Hilton, Margery: The Beach of Sweet Returns. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 306)
  - Harlequin Romance 1951. Pargeter, Margaret: Ride a Black Horse. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1952. Dingwell, Joyce: Corporation Boss. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 307)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233380
  - Harlequin Romance 1953. Reid, Henrietta: Love's Puppet. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1954. Neels, Betty: A Star Looks Down. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 308)
  - Harlequin Romance 1955. Stratton, Rebecca: Moon Tide. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1956. Corrie, Jane: The Impossible Boss. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Harlequin Romance 1957. Rome, Margaret: Valley of Paradise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1958. Gillen, Lucy: All the Long Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - Harlequin Romance 1959. Peters, Sue: Deep Furrows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1960. Doyle, Amanda: Return to Tuckarimba. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Harlequin Romance 1961. Dingwell, Joyce: Deep in the Forest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1962. Baumann, Margaret: Debt of Honor. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 312)
  - Harlequin Romance 1963. Arbor, Jane: Smoke into Flame. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1964. Burchell, Mary: Under the Stars of Paris. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Harlequin Romance 1965. Whistler, Mary: Escape to Happiness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1966. Cork, Dorothy: Red Diamond. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 314)
  - Harlequin Romance 1967. Thorpe, Kay: Sugar Cane Harvest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1968. Wibberley, Mary: The Wilderness Hut. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 315)
  - Harlequin Romance 1969. Britt, Katrina: The Spanish Grandee. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1971. Malcolm, Margaret: The Hearthfire Grows. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 316)
  - Harlequin Romance 1972. Ashton, Elizabeth: Lady in the Limelight. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1973. Pargeter, Margaret: The Kilted Stranger. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 317)
  - Harlequin Romance 1974. Way, Margaret: A Lesson in Loving. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1975. Peters, Sue: Clouded Waters. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 318)
  - Harlequin Romance 1976. Stratton, Rebecca: The Goddess of Mavisu. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1977. Kidd, Flora: The Dance of Courtship. (Harlequin Books) (Box 14, Folder 319)
  - Harlequin Romance 1978. Cork, Dorothy: The Eye of the Sun. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1979. Gillen, Lucy: A Handful of Stars. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 320)
  - Harlequin Romance 1980. Mayo, Margaret: Destiny Paradise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1981. Dingwell, Joyce: The New Broom. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 321)
  - Harlequin Romance 1982. Cust, Barbara: Scent of the Maquis. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1983. Ford, Norrey: The Love Goddess. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 322)
  - Harlequin Romance 1984. Lane, Roumelia: The Tenant of San Mateo. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1985. Clemence, Ruth: Wife Made to Measure. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 323)
  - Harlequin Romance 1986. Carter, Rosemary: Man of the Wild. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1987. Neels, Betty: The Moon for Lavinia. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 324)
  - Harlequin Romance 1988. Seale, Sara: My Heart's Desire (original title: Spread Your Wings). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1989. Ashton, Elizabeth: My Lady Disdain. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 325)
  - Harlequin Romance 1990. Thorpe, Kay: The Royal Affair. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1991. Stratton, Rebecca: Isle of the Golden Drum. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 326)
  - Harlequin Romance 1992. Smith, Doris E.: Smuggled Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1993. Donnelly, Jane: Dark Pursuer. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 327)
  - Harlequin Romance 1994. Wibberley, Mary: The Whispering Gate. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1995. Gillen, Lucy: The Hungry Tide. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 328)
  - Harlequin Romance 1996. Mayo, Margaret: Shades of Autumn. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1997. Chace, Isobel: Singing in the Wilderness. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 329)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233398
  - Harlequin Romance 1997. Chace, Isobel: Singing in the Wilderness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1998. Dingwell, Joyce: The Road Boss. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - Harlequin Romance 1999. Kidd, Flora: The Summer Wife. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2000. Summers, Essie: Not By Appointment. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 331)
  - Harlequin Romance 2001. Reid, Henrietta: Greek Bridal. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2002. Whittal, Yvonne: The Slender Thread. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 332)
  - Harlequin Romance 2004. Beaty, Betty: Head of Chancery. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2005. Weston, Sophie: Goblin Court. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 333)
  - Harlequin Romance 2006. Stratton, Rebecca: Proud Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2007. Lynne, Suzanna: Beloved Viking. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 334)
  - Harlequin Romance 2008. Bevan, Gloria: Dolphin Bay. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2009. Neels, Betty: Esmeralda. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 335)
  - Harlequin Romance 2010. Bianchin, Helen: Bewildered Haven. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2011. Danbury, Iris: The Windmill of Kalakos. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 336)
  - Harlequin Romance 2012. Gillen, Lucy: Return to Deepwater. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2013. Westwood, Gwen: Blossoming Gold. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 337)
  - Harlequin Romance 2014. Gray, Janice: Moonglade. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2015. Douglas, Sheila: Sherringdon Hall. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 338)
  - Harlequin Romance 2016. Way, Margaret: Flight into Yesterday. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2017. Britt, Katrina: The Emerald Garden. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 339)
  - Harlequin Romance 2018. Stratton, Rebecca: Chateau D'Armor. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2019. Allyne, Kerry: Summer Rainfall. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 340)
  - Harlequin Romance 2020. Corrie, Jane: Rainbow for Megan. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2021. Summers, Essie: Beyond the Foothills. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 341)
  - Harlequin Romance 2022. Pargeter, Margaret: Hold Me Captive. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2023. Chace, Isobel: The Clouded Veil. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 342)